

DANIEL TERAN

WEB/SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | PHOENIX, AZ DANIEL-TERAN.COM | GITHUB.COM/EARTHMAN12

PROFILE

Organized, self-motivated, and intuitive individual with experience in a variety of trades from development to engineering. Outfitted with a diverse background obtained from attending university for an extended period as well as a working for a research group for over five years.

SKILLS

- **-Languages:** Python, C/C++, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- -Back-end Frameworks: Django
- -Front-end Frameworks: React, Angular IS, Bootstrap

Developed apps and web pages that implement RESTful API's and SOL databases. Proficient with MS Office. Github and CAD. Great people skills. Eager to learn. Clean and hardworking. Up to date with technology.

EXPERIENCE

RESEARCH TECHNICIAN • UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA: LUNAR & PLANETARY LAB • AUGUST 2016 - PRESENT

Wrote scripts and GUIs in Python using Tkinter, PyQt, MatPlotLib, AstroPy and many other libraries for our scientific research. Designed space flight hardware using CAD for NASA and JPL as well as lab specific projects. Aligned and tested optical setups in and out of our sounding rocket. Maintained our team's weekly schedule online.

STUDENT WORKER • UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA: FUEL MODERN **EATERY • FEBRUARY 2015 - NOVEMBER 2016**

Rotated between shifts working as a cashier, line cook, and smoothie maker. Assisted in opening and closing the restaurant which consisted of prepping food, cleaning the kitchen/dining floor, restocking, and counting the drawer.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF GENERAL STUDIES IN SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGY, **HEALTH & SOCIETY • AUGUST 2012 - MAY 2018 • UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA**

Studied Math, Computer Science, Physics/Astrophysics, Materials Engineering, Sociology and Astronomy





